A Guide to the Mann Page Papers, 1766-1813
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
- Account of John Miller to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1804. (Folder 27)
- Account of Benjamin Hope to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1804. (Folder 27)
- Account of Mordecai Cook to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1804. (Folder 27)
- Causes for trial, November 1804. (Folder 27)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Wright, 12 January 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Williams E. Davis, 30 January 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipt from Peter Robert Deneufville to Mann Page, 6 February 1805. (Folder 28)
- Account of John Sinclair with the sheriff of Gloucester County, March 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipted account of E. Williams with George Finch, 13 April 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John D. Gressell, 13 July 1805. (Folder 28)
- Nathaniel Burwell, Carter Hall, to Mann Page, Shelly, 25 August 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with T. Minor, 22 October 1805. (Folder 28)
- Account of George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester, November 1805. (Folder 28)
- Account of John Bracken to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1805. (Folder 28)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with John Donaghey, 15 February 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipted account of Page with John Donaghey, 15 February 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipted account of Page with the post office, 22 March 1806. (Folder 29)
- Account of R. Thronton with Martin Fisk, 1 June 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with post office, Gloucester, 21 June 1806. (Folder 29)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipt from Francis Page to Mann Page, 10 July 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipted account of the estate of Robert Page with John Grant, 21 July 1806. (Folder 29)
- Philip Nelson to Mann Page, 26 July 1806. (Folder 29)
- Receipted account of Mann Page to Charles M. McPherson, 28 October 1806. (Folder 30)
- Account of Benjamin Hope to the clerk of Gloucester County, October 1806. (Folder 30)
- Account of George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester County, October 1806. (Folder 30)
- Account of Mann Page with J. Chew, 27 November 1806. (Folder 30)
- John Cooper to Mrs. Houghton, 16 December 1806. (Folder 30)
- Account of Jasper C. Rowe to the clerk of Gloucester County, December 1806. (Folder 30)
- Account of John Ransome to the clerk of Gloucester County, December 1806. (Folder 30)
- Joseph Cooper to Mrs. Houghton, 19 January 1807. (Folder 31)
- John Cooper to Mrs. Houghton, 22 January 1807. (Folder 31)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Thomas Smith and Co., 25 April 1807. (Folder 31)
- Mann Page to Robert Nelson, York Town, 25 May 1807. (Folder 31)
- Daniel Judds notes for suit, 8 June 1807. (Folder 31)
- Receipted account of Page with Dodge and Cobb, 22 September 1807. (Folder 31)
- Account of Morgan with Tomkies to the clerk of Gloucester County, September 1807. (Folder 31)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with W. Taliaferro, 10 November 1807. (Folder 31)
- Account of Charles James to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1807. (Folder 31)
- Account of William Richardson to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1807. (Folder 31)
- Account of James Madison et al. to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1807. (Folder 31)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with the College of William & Mary, 1 December 1807. (Folder 31)
- Receipt from N. Taylor to Mann Page, 1 January 1808. (Folder 32)
- Receipt from William Pippin to Mann Page, 20 January 1808. (Folder 32)
- Receipted account of William Minor with Simon Block, 4 March 1808. (Folder 32)
- Charles Coughton to John Chew, Urbanna, 29 March 1808. (Folder 32)
- Judith Grymes to Mann Page, 29 March 1808. (Folder 32)
- Note from Elizabeth Page, 2 April 1808. (Folder 32)
- Aphia Houghton to Robert Nelson, Little York, 23 April 1808. (Folder 32)
- Alexander E. Lincoln to Mann Page, 9 May 1808. (Folder 32)
- Account of Mann Page with John Powell, 1 August 1808. (Folder 32)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with the post office, 28 September 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of John Martin to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of Carter B. Berkeley to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of Lewis Chapman to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1808. (Folder 33)
- Account of Charles James to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1808. (Folder 33)
- Receipt from Duneuf Germain, 1 February 1809. (Folder 34)
- Bonds and accounts Elizabeth City Court, 13 February 1809. (Folder 34)
- Receipted account of Page with Nathaniel Taylor, 19 February 1809. (Folder 34)
- Memorandum, 29 December 1809. (Folder 34)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester, 1809. (Folder 34)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Alexander Brodie, 1809. (Folder 34)
- Account of Charles James to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 34)
- Account of Morgan Tomkies to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 34)
- Account of Morgan Tomkies to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of William K. Pinn to Nathaniel Burwell, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of Greenhow and Cole to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of John Spalding to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of James Jones to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of Henry Wests and Thomas Wests to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Receipted account of Page with Alexander Brodie, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, 1809. (Folder 35)
- Sarah Cary to John Page, Gloster, 6 February 1810. (Folder 36)
- Receipts from Francis Page to Mann Page, 20 March 1810. (Folder 36)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- Account of Southy Mouning to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- Thomas Sampson to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- Morgan Tomkies to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- John Robins and Martha, his wife, to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester, 1810. (Folder 36)
- Mutual Assurance Society to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1810. (Folder 37)
- John Bracken to the clerk of Gloucester, October 1810. (Folder 37)
- John Spalding to the clerk of Gloucester, November 1810. (Folder 37)
- Morgan Tomkies to the clerk of Gloucester, November 1810. (Folder 37)
- Greenhow and Cole to the clerk of Gloucester, November 1810. (Folder 37)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to William Hale, 1810. (Folder 37)
- Martin Fisk and Co., Norfolk, to Mann Page, Gloucester, 13 April 1911., Contains one enclosure. (Folder 38)
- Account of Mann Page with M. Fisk and Co., 13 April 1811., Enclosed with the previous item. (Folder 38)
- Note from Mann Page to William Harwood, 13 April 1811. (Folder 38)
- Note from Mann Page to Southy Mouning, 16 April 1811. (Folder 38)
  Receipted 15 June.
- Note from Mann Page to Southy Mouning, 16 April 1811. (Folder 38)
- Account of Thomas West to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1811. (Folder 38)
- Account of John Lewis and J. F. Lewis to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- . J. F. Lewis to the clerk of the Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- John Lewis to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- John Bracken to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- William Yates to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- James Belsches to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- Mutual Assurance Society to the clerk of Gloucester Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- Account of John Sinclair to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, May 1811. (Folder 38)
- Mann Page to William Wilkins, 3 June 1811. (Folder 39)
  Receipted.
- Order from Southy Mouning to Mann Page, 17 June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with Duneut Germain, 17 June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of Thomas Sampson to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of William K. Mackinder to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of John Fleming to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1811. (Folder 39)
- Judgement, 4 August 1811. (Folder 39)
  Concerns Greenhow v. Sterling etc.
- Account of Henry Crewdson etc. to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1811. (Folder 39)
- John Bracken to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1811. (Folder 39)
- Mortecai Cook to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, August 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of Greenhow and Cole to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1811. (Folder 39)
- John Spalding to the clerk of Gloucester, November 1811. (Folder 39)
- Reubin Thorton, George F. Washington, Charles A. Washington, etc. to the clerk of Gloucester County, December 1811. (Folder 39)
- Conquest Royston to the clerk of Gloucester County, December 1811. (Folder 39)
- Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester County, December 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to William Hall, 1811. (Folder 39)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to William Hall, 1811. (Folder 39)
- A list of fees due Mann Page from Robert Greenhow, 1811. (Folder 39)
- William Camp and Sterling Seawell to the clerk of Gloucester County, March 1812. (Folder 40)
- Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, June 1812. (Folder 40)
- Reubin Thornton etc. to the clerk of Gloucester County, September 1812. (Folder 40)
- George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester County, October 1812. (Folder 40)
- Bill to Elay Balderston from Warner and Hanna, 12 October 1812. (Folder 40)
- Benjamin Blake to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, October 1812. (Folder 40)
- Israel and John P. Pleasants to the clerk of Gloucester Superior Court, October 1812. (Folder 40)
- Account of Robert Greenhow to the clerk of Gloucester County, November 1812. (Folder 40)
- James Miller to the clerk of Gloucester County, February 1813. (Folder 41)
- Conquest Royston to the clerk of Gloucester County, February 1813. (Folder 41)
- John Walker to the clerk of Gloucester County, February 1813. (Folder 41)
- William Yates and John Mitchell to the clerk of Gloucester County, March 1813. (Folder 41)
- John R. Cary to the clerk of Gloucester County, March 1813. (Folder 41)
- Charles C. Edwards to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- George Hatton to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- William Leigh, York, to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- John Bassett to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- Susan Nuttall to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- John Fisher and Edward Fisher to the clerk of Gloucester County, April 1813. (Folder 41)
- William Jackman etc. to the clerk of Gloucester County, May 1813. (Folder 41)
- Thomas Ransome Jr. to the clerk of Gloucester County, May 1813. (Folder 41)
- Miles Camp to the clerk of Gloucester County, May 1813. (Folder 41)
- Joseph Monnett to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1813. (Folder 42)
- Thomas Jones and William Jones and William Field to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1813. (Folder 42)
- William Thornton and William Stubblefield to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1813. (Folder 42)
- Auston Brockenbrough to the clerk of Gloucester County, June 1813. (Folder 42)
- Thomas H. Dilliard to the clerk of Gloucester County, July 1813. (Folder 42)
- Daniel McNaughton to the clerk of Gloucester County, July 1813. (Folder 42)
- Thomas Rilie to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- Robert Brooking to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- Edward Shurls to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- Thomas Rilie to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- William Yates to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- John Davis to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- Suzanna Yates to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- John Dawson to the clerk of Gloucester County, August 1813. (Folder 42)
- Thomas Jones and William Stubblefield to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1813. (Folder 42)
- John R. Cary and Robert Cary to the clerk of Gloucester County, 1813. (Folder 42)
- Copy of statement, January 1814. (Folder 43)
  Concerns Robert Greenhow v. Sterling and Seawell.
- Account of Mann Page to Robert West, 2 February 1815. (Folder 43)
- Copy of a letter sent from Gloucester to Robert Greenhow, 29 March 1816. (Folder 43)
- Account of John Gressett to the sheriff, 15 June 1817. (Folder 43)
- Account of Mann Page to the clerk of Gloucester, 1825. (Folder 43)
- Receipted account of Mann Page with William Prosser, 15 December 1826. (Folder 43)
- Receipted account of Mann Page for taxes, 1826. (Folder 43)
- Memorandum, 17 September 1829. (Folder 43)
- Memorandum, 17 October 1829. (Folder 43)
- Account of William Page with William P. Smith and Co, 16 January 1830. (Folder 44)
- Account of William Page to John M. Botts, 1830. (Folder 44)
- Account, 13 January 1831. (Folder 44)
  Account of the sales of stock & plantation utensils at New Cap Quarter belonging to the estate of William M. Page, deceased.
- Account, 7 March 1831. (Folder 44)
  Account of oxen to be sold at Gloucester Court House.
- Check of Holt and Otey to Saunders and Irby, 11 May 1854., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 44)
- Protest against a bill of exchange by Jonathan Ely, 14 September 1854., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Folder 44)
- Copy of assessment against John Tabb, 1860. (Folder 44)
- Receipt from W. C. Carrington to William Barge, 22 June 1869. (Folder 44)
- Anderson. (Folder 45)
- Account of Mann Page with Ambrose Anderson. (Folder 45)
- Account of Mann Page with William Denis. (Folder 45)
- Account of John Page with Edward Field. (Folder 45)
- Philip Grymes to [Mann Page] (Folder 45)
- Receipt from Bart Harvey. (Folder 45)
- Memorandum. Heathcoat Dall, B. Billeps. (Folder 45)
- Account of Hudgin. (Folder 45)
- Account of Charles James to the clerk of Gloucester. (Folder 45)
- John D. Jarvis to [Mann Page] (Folder 45)
- A. Kevan to Mann Page. (Folder 45)
- Receipt. Mann Page to William Lucas. (Folder 45)
- Receipt from William Lucas to Mann Page. (Folder 45)
- Account of William Lucas to Mann Page. (Folder 45)
- Account of Mann Page with Josias Moody. (Folder 46)
- Account of Mann Page with clerk of Williamsburg District Court. (Folder 46)
- Page's account of cash and tobacco. (Folder 46)
- Statement of accounts between Thomas Whiting, merchant, and Mann Page. (Folder 46)
- Reynolds memorandum. (Folder 46)
- Receipt from Auguston Smith to Mann Page. (Folder 46)
- Receipt from Nathaniel Taylor to Mann Page, Jr. (Folder 46)
- W. Thornton to [Mann Page] (Folder 46)
- Memorandum of Walker's money. (Folder 46)
- 2 memorandums. (Folder 46)
- Chart of the road from Ridge Way in Caroline to the main road in Hanover. (Folder 46)
- Letter fragment. (Folder 46)
- Letter. (Folder 46)
- Poem. (Folder 46)
- Poem. (Folder 46)
- Memo. (Folder 46)
- Memo with two labels. (Folder 46)
- Coversheet. (Folder 46)
- Coversheet. (Folder 46)
- Coversheet. (Folder 46)
- Manuscript copy of a speech., 12 pages. (Folder 47)
- Interpretation of the Bible., 20 pages. (Folder 47)
- Interpretation of the Bible., 22 pages. (Folder 47)
- Excerpts from Roman History., 20 pages. (Folder 47)
- Memorandum. Book on accounts., 36 pages. (Folder 47)